[{"answer": "OGERS: Well, as a former law enforcement agent, much like the crime scene photo where you would see a victim who had been -- had suffered gunshots to the head.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Can you describe them to me?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "I mean are they, would you say, similar to the images we've seen of the other victims of the raid?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Yes, I think they're fairly tough to look at.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "I mean, would you argue personally that they are just from a taste point of view too graphic, too gruesome, to be published?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, on the operation, it was a great tribute to the president's courage that he ordered this operation.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "Look, what's your take on all this?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "The issue I think is more a question of, would it affect national security and would it put our troop's lives at risk if you inflame the Muslim community by publishing them?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "So the morality of all this is a little bit skewed, to put it mildly, isn't it?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "Most people here are sick and tired of him and what he's brought to the country.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "I mean, what kind of reputation did he have by the end amongst the Pakistani community?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Well, of course, I'm tempted to say that you know if somebody wants to leak me the photos exclusively, then hey, you know, give me a call at the office.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "Why on this occasion would you prefer it not to be?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "Well, look, I mean, we're in -- we're in the business of getting information out.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "I mean, would \"The New York Times\" have published these pictures if they'd been offered to them?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "I think it's a terrible mistake.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "What is your reaction to the news that they won't be published?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Under the First Amendment, that's the wrong question.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "What do we really gain by seeing an image of that given we know that's what happened?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Do you agree with him?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, I don't really buy that.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "What do you say to that, Nick Kristof?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "If it went down that the way the administration says it went down, it was lawful.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "In your legal opinion, was it lawful?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Well, it's one of many positions where we're just completely hypocritical.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "That, in terms of morality, seems a pretty flawed double position, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "Yes, there certainly have been doubts about whether it really was bin Laden who's been killed.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Isn't it the easier thing to just say, you know what, here he is, move on?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "We apply a double standard on outrage.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Aren't they entitled to an image to atone for all the terrible images he inflicted on the American people?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Let me ask Alan Dershowitz one difficult question, which is this, which is, if the military, as we understand, made a plea for these photographs not to be released, because they genuinely feared there would be reprisals against servicemen in Afghanistan and Iraq, is that not a compelling reason alone not to publish them?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "I felt happy that the man who bragged and said that he killed my son, like Khalid Sheikh Mohammed did at Guantanamo, bragging that they killed my son and 3,000 other innocent American whose only crime was they went to work -- I felt good about it.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "What were your feelings when you first heard bin Laden was dead?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Would it give you any kind of solace?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "Well, as Jim just said, I'm going to believe the president, take him at his word.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Without a picture, are you entirely satisfied that it was bin Laden, that he is dead?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "I think I can speak for so many families that since about 11:00 on Sunday night, it's been quite a wild ride of emotions and exhaustion.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "How will you be feeling tomorrow when this very emotional visit takes place?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "My feelings are I want to extend my internal gratitude to President Obama for having the backbone to make the attack and get bin Laden and take him out, like he promised to us before.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "What will your feelings be?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "I can understand him not releasing the photo.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "Brandon, when you hear the president talk about the morality of not releasing this picture, of doing the right thing, it's not what America does, what is your take, given you were at Guantanamo watching and witnessing some pretty outrageous stuff being carried out in America's name?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "But in relation to what you witnessed -- I mean, you saw, I would argue from what I read of your testimony before, flagrant abuses of the Geneva Convention and of justice, didn't you?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110504pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "For everything that you saw, do you think that torture in any guise, whether it's semi-permissible, like waterboarding -- does it ever work, from what you saw?", "qSentId": 605}]